sup everyone T 5 here with a very
special video today that's right it's
the 2023 Christmas Haul woo let's open
some friends I I'm going to do
something special this year that I
haven't ever done before for Christmas
I'm going to open all my PLS right here
on camera so you guys can witness my
excitement firsthand and before we open
it can we just give a shout out to my
mama cuz a like you went all out
with the with the like Gift
Rap this year like this is like the
first year in like five or six years
when my mom actually use give ra and
normally she just throws everything
in like shopping bags and that's fine
but damn if this doesn't get me in the
Christmas period am I right everyone now
I I'm I'm just gonna I'm just going to
open this one first because to be
completely honest like I know what the
it is like what me and Mom we a
cheer dog so like like yeah like
she like she always gets me like a like
a ton of cans of chili no beans and
let's let's check this
out this is baked
beans no don't tell me these are all
baked beans I can't put not sh
[Applause]
on I'm going to have to talk to my mom
about that God damn okay we're just
ignoring what that present but it's okay
it's okay like we know there's going to
be a lot of sock up in this
oh yeah let's see what this
is what the
what in God's green
earth this isn't S onr this is
Star
Wars
mama you didn't get me so G you said you
were getting all Sonic
Underground I'm going to talk to
you in a bit you wa
upstairs yeah but like let's open the
next one she okay she said this one's
going to get me really excited and I
believe
her like her she left me a not to it
says like I know how much you love
soccer underr for some reason so I got
you the Sonic underr plushies now you
all know you all know I have been wa
waiting a long time to get the knuckles
Danny plushy so I'm really excited for
this like it can only be AA Danny
plushy or or like Knuckles plushy you
know what the I mean and I already
got socks so it's got me
knuckles
what the
I mean it's pink like Sonia but
that's not Sonic
Underground what's the other
one what that's a son
either is it supposed to be madic and
Sonia hold on hold hold hold the up
okay my mom said this is a twout gift so
I feel like this this is going to be
talk this is probably a joke so
let's
[Applause]
see is this supposed to be
Sonic this this is haunted what
the
is this only Sonic cuz it's
blue what what the is this this
isn't sock
underground I want the sock Underground
I want the sock
underground God
damn what do I do with all
these I don't play with dolls I'm a man
I'm a man who likes Sonic
Underground
damn my mama's messing everything up she
always
does what the is
this all these zombies talk on
DVDs Playstation All Stars Battle
Royale holy
Mojo Zach Bell Mota Fury maybe my mom
did do some good holy I got to look
at this right now
why is that
Mojo did my mom put it in the wrong
container I'm going to play Zach go
right now it's probably in
here what the
this better not be empty too what
what is my mom
doing did my mom up did you buy
these at the Goodwill
I'm so confused I don't know
what to do do I just stop with the
video cuz this is not like a Sonic grab
like Christmas Bonanza this is not the
son on Christmas hours waiting
for what
is I know how much you like mag the
Hedgehog for some reason so here are
some
stickers you know I do mama
you know I love Mac that talk up in this
oh yes oh I love Manic the
Hedgehog this is Ron Weasley from the
deathly
holos it's a double siiz scker
tool how some sticker things what is
this
what's
this that's a slightly younger younger
Ron Weasley that's time is underground
what is
this are you kidding me I'm
sending that back to the good well cuz
you know that's when my mom bought that
okay I guess we got one
present okay she said this is going to
be the big one so I feel like it's got
to be like at leas a socer on
[Applause]
DVD The Action
Bible what is The Action Bible I'm not
religious the only Bible I know is the
Sonic Underground
Bible what the this is a this is a
this is the Bible I
don't need this I don't even I don't
even watch the babble I only watch Sonic
[Applause]
Underground what do I do this was
supposed to be the sock on Christmas
Christmas Bonanza what the do I do
now
damn